Good morning!
Where are you guys now?
Osaka!
We're in front of the Tenka Club.
You're wearing your own clothes today.
From the costume of the shoot?
It's not this.
It's not good.
I'm wearing it.
I'm going to coordinate with a
professional.
A professional?
I'm happy.
I think it's a good idea.
The backstabbing backstabbing Osaka Deep
Rocker of Batten Girls' Squad!
The backstabbing backstabbing of Batten
Girls' Squad this time is
Osaka Deep Rocker is fine.
Get a program award by getting Osaka's
sister to dress up in Osaka.
To enjoy Osaka gourmet,
I tried too cool retro game,
Gambler Riko appeared in the gambler
spirit,
Miracles were repeated in the first
shuriken,
Finally, the members are excited about
the finish of the gete that made it a
round.
Please watch the deep location of
Moridakusan to the end.
Batten Shoujitai's
Uragaishite! Batten!
First, the members came to the clothes
shop called Naniwakomachi.
They are introduced to many TV shows.
They are going to have a powerful mom to
dress up as a model for the members.
Let's take a look at the clothes.
Yes, please.
Please think about it and take a look.
I think I can get a good result from
this.
What is this?
Red?
Which one is it?
This one.
Oishi-san!
We transformed!
Gao!
Wonderful!
Yay!
Wow!
This is Blue.
She is wearing a spankol.
She is not afraid of Christmas.
She is wearing a blue spankol.
Behind her is a lion.
Lion.
Lion is a lion.
She is so cute.
Her katsu is also cute.
Pink.
This is a tiger.
Look at her eyes.
She is so cute.
She is wearing a pink dress.
And behind her is a white tiger.
She is so cute.
She is amazing.
Why?
Next is the red one.
I was wearing a black skirt.
Red and black.
It's hot.
I can't say anything about the food.
Thank you.
I think we can go to Halloween.
Shall we go to Halloween?
Green is here.
She is amazing.
She is a zoo.
She is so cute.
Purple.
It is difficult to call her purple.
But she often wears purple.
She wore purple pink.
She is so cute.
She is so elegant.
Ready, go!
Gyaooo!
The members who transformed into Osaka
costumes
are moving to a new world with a lot of
tourists.
They are seen a lot and they are spoken
a lot, so they stand out a lot.
The members were quite embarrassed.
How was it, everyone?
Walking in the new world?
I was a little brave.
Everyone saw the world.
I was called Akazu Kin-chan.
How was it?
I felt like I became a famous person.
I was surprised.
This time, we will have a deep video.
We will play a game called Smart Ball.
Smart Ball?
I've never heard of it.
Me too.
Next, we arrived at the smart ball,
which is popular in retro games.
This game is a pinball game.
You can get 25 balls for 100 yen.
This is a pinball game.
It's a fun game that even children can
play, but you can't play it if you're
under 18 years old.
So this time, Rirua and Miyu can't get
in.
Too bad.
If you play the game, you'll know.
You can get the ball in the end.
Yes.
The number of balls and the price of the
card.
The amount of balls and the price of the
card will be decided.
OI-SAN
Start!
Go for it!
Wow!
What's going on?
I think I can put it in!
Go for it!
It's so easy!
Oh! It's so easy!
Go for it!
Go! Go! Go!
Wow!
It's so easy!
You are doing great!
You are getting better and better!
I see.
30 seconds left.
Oh! Wow!
It's amazing!
It's a chance!
It's so easy!
Wow!
Oh!
It's wonderful!
It's so easy!
It's 58 balls!
OI-SAN
Start!
Go for it!
It's so hard!
Wow!
It's a chance!
Go for it!
What the hell is this?
It's a chance!
Wow!
It's so easy!
Can't believe it!
It'll be gone
for this one ball
As a gambler,
I'm so scared.
I want to put my hands in the water.
I can't.
My hands are shaking.
Your hands are shaking.
You can stop but you can't stop.
I can't stop.
I still have one more chance.
I'm done.
How many points?
0 points.
I'm in trouble.
OI-SAN
I'm going to start.
I'll do my best.
I'm still in the water.
I want to put my hands in the water.
RIKO is a gambler.
Please, This happens every time.
The conditional route is too hard to
Grand Jirakudasui, so I will return.
You are weak!
Oh!
You won't be able to do the
1 minute left.
OK.
I can't do it.
10 seconds left.
9, 8,
3, 2, 1,
Time's up!
How many did you get?
Oh!
I got it!
How many did you get?
Wow!
That's a lot!
I got it!
So, there are three cards.
100 yen
500 yen
10 yen
Wow!
10 yen!
The number of the cards and the money.
I see.
Who will win?
Sakura will win!
But...
I'm sorry!
I'm too responsible!
I want Riko to win!
I'm sorry!
OK!
I won!
Ready?
Go!
I won!
Amazing!
I'm sorry!
I'm glad!
I won!
Oisa!
Thank you for waiting!
I won!
The two who couldn't get into the smart
ball challenge the shuriken!
If you get stuck in the frame, you get
1000 yen per piece!
But this is pretty hard, isn't it?
OI-SAN!
Ready, set, go!
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!
It's a little higher!
It's not reaching the target. If it's
around here, it's gonna work.
Oh, I see.
Ready, set, go!
AHHHHHHHHHHHHH!
Oh no!
That was close!
Ready, set, go!
AHHHHHHHHH!
That was close!
A little higher!
AHHHHHHHHH!
That was close!
Oh no!
AHHHHHHHHH!
That was close!
But there's still a lot left.
I'm sure I can get it.
Ready, set, go!
AHHHHHHHHH!
That was close!
Mori-chan, you have to get all of them.
6,000 yen.
Good luck!
You can get all of them.
First round!
I got it!
You got it!
AHHHHHHHHH!
I'm gonna get it!
I got it!
I think I can get it.
Ready, set, go!
AHHHHHHHHH!
I got it!
3 more to go.
I'm gonna get it in the middle.
Ready, set, go!
AHHHHHHHHH!
I got it!
Ready, set, go!
AHHHHHHHHH!
What's this?
I got a B!
AHHHHHHHHH!
Last round!
I'm gonna get it in the middle.
No!
Wow!
You got it in the middle.
You're a ninja!
The members who got the money were
invited to the Kushi-katsu shop in
Osaka.
The shop we visited this time is in the
center of the new world, Kushi-katsu
Yokozuna.
If you come to this shop, you can find
everything from delicious Kushi-katsu
fried in Osaka to Kushi-katsu from
Kawaridani to anything.
I found a menu that I was curious about.
I got a menu.
Ta-da!
Total of 11,800 yen!
Wow!
I got a menu.
I'm glad.
O-SHA!
Thank you for your hard work in Osaka
D-PRO!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you!
I'm going to give you a present.
I got a menu.
It's my first time to eat Kushi-Katsu
here.
I'm nervous.
I'm going to eat this.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please tell us how to eat this.
Please tell us.
I can't eat it.
I'll give you a discount if you eat as
much as you want.
I can't put it on my hands, so I'll just
do it once.
One, two, three!
How much is it?
As much as you like.
It looks delicious.
Let's eat!
Oh, it's good!
How is it?
Is it good?
It's hot!
It's good!
It's a good opportunity!
There is a slightly different finish.
I will review what this is and everyone
will guess it.
Oh, you won't tell me?
There is a sauce for the water.
I think I know the answer, so I don't
like it.
I don't like it.
I don't like it if you know the answer
correctly.
Oishaa!
What should I do?
Do you think it's hard?
The first one?
I think the belly is better.
What is the belly?
Exactly!
The middle.
It may be white fish.
Yes, it is white fish.
I'm hungry.
Don't say anything inside.
It looks delicious.
I'll put more.
Let's eat.
It's good.
Is it good?
It looks delicious.
I don't know.
It's good.
It's like fish.
It's like meat.
It's good.
I'll eat it.
What do you think it is?
Frog!
What was that?
It's a frog!
What is the point?
You should eat more.
It's delicious.
Frogs are often taken care of.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm hungry.
I'm going to eat this.
This is amazing.
It's really good.
Is it good?
Yes.
I'm surprised.
Did you get a bite?
It's like a whale.
The taste of the fish is strange.
I may be able to eat it for the first
time.
It's not meat or fish.
But it's elastic.
It's delicious.
Do you want to try?
I'm fine.